Guide to the Richard Henry Pratt Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- General Correspondence and Official Papers, 1867-1924; Series I; (74 boxes)
  - INCOMING LETTERS
    - Ironie, Kate, 1 item, 1887 (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - "J" general, 18 items, 1878-1920 (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - Jackson, Sheldon, 9 items, 1880-1904 (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - Jay, John, 1 item, 1890
    - Johnson, Albert, 2 items, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - Johnson, Edwin S., 2 items, 1917
    - Johnston, Herbert, 4 items, 1903-08 (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - Jones, William A., 6 items, 1897 (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - Jones, William A., 17 items, 1898 (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - Jones, William A., 10 items, 1899 (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - Jones, William A., 17 items, 1900-01 (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - Jones, William A., 15 items, 1902 (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - Jones, William A., 7 items, 1903, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - "Ka-Ke" general, 12 items, 1875-1923 (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - "Ki-Kr" general, 17 items, 1879-1922, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - Kelly, M. Clyde, 22 items, 1921-23 (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - Kennedy, M. C., 1 item, 1901 (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - Kennedy, Thomas B., 15 items, 1880-1904, n.d.
    - Kidd, Meredith H., 1 item, 1894 (Box 4, Folder 150)
    - King, William H., 1 item, 1921
    - Kitch, James B.
      See: Nettie McDonald, Box 5, folder 182
    - Knox, Philander C., 2 items, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 151)
    - Kohpay, Harry, 5 items, 1891-1923
    - "La" general, 18 items, 1887-1923, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - "Le-Ly" general, 18 items, 1879-1923, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - Lacey, John F., 1 item, 1903 (Box 4, Folder 154)
    - LaFlesche, Rosa B., 5 items, 1913-21
    - Lane, Franklin K., 18 items, 1913-18 (Box 5, Folder 155)
    - Lane, Harry, 3 items, 1915-16 (Box 5, Folder 156)
    - Lane, W. B., 2 items, 1879 (Box 5, Folder 157)
    - Lanier, Sidney, 1 item, 1875
    - Larocque, Annie S., 20 items, 1878-89 (Box 5, Folder 158)
    - Larocque, Annie S., 19 items, 1892-1903, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 159)
    - Larocque, Joseph, 4 items, 1879, 1893 (Box 5, Folder 160)
    - Latimer, Joseph W., 11 items, 1914, 1922-23 (Box 5, Folder 161)
    - Lea, Isaac, 1 item, 1876 (Box 5, Folder 162)
    - Lee, Fitzhugh, 4 items, 1895-96
    - Lee, Jessie M. and Lucy W., 5 items, 1885-1922 (Box 5, Folder 163)
    - Lenroot, Irvine L., 2 items, 1921, 1923
    - Lente, The Rev. James R., 1 item, 1890 (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - Lillibridge, Annie, 1 item, 1896
    - Linnen, E. B., 2 items, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 165)
    - Linton, William S., 2 items, 1896
    - Lippincott, J. A., 20 items, 1882-98 (Box 5, Folder 166)
    - Lippincott, J. A., 22 items, 1898-1905, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 167)
    - Lipps, O. H., 17 items, 1914-16 (Box 5, Folder 168)
    - The Literary Society, Washington, D.C.
      See: W. E. Safford, Box 8, folder 272
    - Lockwood, George B., 7 items, 1920-22 (Box 5, Folder 169)
    - Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1 item, 1903
    - Logan, Howard, G., 3 items, 1891 (Box 5, Folder 170)
    - Lone Wolf, 1 item, 1894
    - Longstreth, Abby A., 2 items, 1888, 1890 (Box 5, Folder 171)
    - Longstreth, S., 1 item, 1891
    - Longstreth, Sara M., 1 item, 1902
    - Longstreth, Susan, 12 items, 1882-92, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 172)
    - Lopp, William T., 1 item, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 173)
    - Los Angeles Times
      See: Harry Chandler, Box 8, folder 56
    - Ludlow, Helen N., 6 items, 1879-80 (Box 5, Folder 174)
    - Lufkins, Wm., 1 item, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 175)
    - "Ma" general, 22 items, 1880-1923, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 176)
    - "Me-Mu" general, 20 items, 1880-1923, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - Mabie, Hamilton W., 1 item, 1892 (Box 5, Folder 178)
    - MacAlister, James, 1 item, 1896
    - McCabe, Charles C., 15 items, 1891-1905 (Box 5, Folder 179)
    - McCammon, Jos. K., 6 items, 1884-99 (Box 5, Folder 180)
    - McCauley, J. A., 11 items, 1880-96
    - McComas, L. E., 1 item, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 181)
    - McCusker, Philip, 8 items, 1875-79
    - McDonald, James A. and Nettie B., 12 items, 1917-23 (Box 5, Folder 182)
    - McDowell, Malcolm, 2 items, 1915-16 (Box 5, Folder 183)
    - McGee, William John, 4 items, 1880-1904 (Box 5, Folder 184)
    - McGillycuddy, V. T., 1 item, n.d.
    - McKenzie, Fayette A,. 18 items, 1904, 1912-15 (Box 5, Folder 185)
    - McKinley, William, 1 item, 1897 (Box 5, Folder 186)
    - McMichael, William, 6 items, 1882-93 (Box 5, Folder 187)
    - The Macmillan Co., 7 items, 1922-23
    - Magill, Edward H., 2 items, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 188)
    - Mah-nim-ick (Manimic), 1 item, 1880
    - Mahon, Thaddeus M., 1 item, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 189)
    - Maish, Levi, 1 item, 1888
    - Mallery, Garrick, 1 item, 1879 (Box 5, Folder 190)
    - Mani, Thomas, 1 item, 1910
    - Mansur, Charles H., 3 items, 1893-94 (Box 6, Folder 191)
    - Marmon, R. G. and S. R., 4 items, 1920, 1923
    - Marsden, Edward, 14 items, 1892-1923 (Box 6, Folder 192)
    - Marshall, James F. B., 2 items, 1879-80 (Box 6, Folder 193)
    - Marshall, Thomas, 1 item, 1898
    - Mason, John C., 1 item, 1904 (Box 6, Folder 194)
    - Mason, Levant L., 6 items, 1903-04
    - Mather, S[ara] A., 15 items, 1878-84, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 195)
    - Matlock, Stacy, 1 item, 1892 (Box 6, Folder 196)
    - Maynard, La Salle A., 2 items, 1903
    - Meritt, E. B., 8 items, 1914-23 (Box 6, Folder 197)
    - Miles, John D., 14 items, 1875-79 (Box 6, Folder 198)
    - Miles, John D., 12 items, 1880-81 (Box 6, Folder 199)
    - Miles, John D., 20 items, 1882-84 (Box 6, Folder 200)
    - Miles, John D., 24 items, 1885, 1887-90 (Box 6, Folder 201)
    - Miles, John D., 19 items, 1891-1901 (Box 6, Folder 202)
    - Miles, John D., 19 items, 1903-07 (Box 6, Folder 203)
    - Miles, John D., 14 items, 1914-16, 1918 (Box 6, Folder 204)
    - Miles, John D. and Margaret H., 23 items, 1919-21, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 205)
    - Miles, Nelson A., 8 items, 1880-1901 (Box 6, Folder 206)
    - Miller, [N. D. W.?], 11 items, 1876-78 (Box 6, Folder 207)
    - Miller, Will H., 8 items, 1904-1920
    - Miller, William E., 15 items, 1895-1917 (Box 6, Folder 208)
    - Miller, William H., 20 items, 1882-83 (Box 6, Folder 209)
    - Miller, William H., 13 items, 1884 (Box 6, Folder 210)
    - Miller, William H., 16 items, 1886-1903 (Box 6, Folder 211)
    - Mills, Clark, 2 items, 1877-78 (Box 6, Folder 212)
    - Milroy, Robert H., 1 item, 1884
    - Montezuma, Carlos, 12 items, 1888-1900 (Box 6, Folder 213)
    - Montezuma, Carlos, 16 items, 1901, 1904-07 (Box 6, Folder 214)
    - Montezuma, Carlos, 11 items, 1908-11, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 215)
    - Montezuma, Carlos, 9 items, 1914 (Box 6, Folder 216)
    - Montezuma, Carlos, 11 items, 1915 (Box 6, Folder 217)
    - Montezuma, Carlos, 13 items, 1916 (Box 6, Folder 218)
    - Montezuma, Carlos, 14 items, 1916-17 (Box 6, Folder 219)
    - Montezuma, Carlos, 14 items, 1918-19 (Box 7, Folder 220)
    - Montezuma, Carlos, 15 items, 1919-20 (Box 7, Folder 221)
    - Montezuma, Carlos, 14 items, 1921-22 (Box 7, Folder 222)
    - Mooney, James
      See: Gertrude Bonnin, Box 1, folder 35
    - Moorehead, Warren K., 2 items, 1910 (Box 7, Folder 223)
    - Morgan, J. H., 1 item, 1920
    - Morgan, Thomas J., 26 items, 1889-1904 (Box 7, Folder 224)
    - Morris, Mary (Mrs. Wistar), 18 items, 1884-1923, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 225)
    - Morris, Wistar, 14 items, 1883-89 (Box 7, Folder 226)
    - Morton, Levi P., 1 item, 1892 (Box 7, Folder 227)
    - Moss, Lemuel, 1 item, 1903
    - "N" general, 17 items, 1883-1923, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 228)
    - Natalish, Vincent, 2 items, 1914-15 (Box 7, Folder 229)
    - The National Republican
      See: George B. Lockwood, Box 5, folder 169
    - National Republican Congressional Committee, 2 items, 1922
    - Nelson, Knute, 19 items, 1897-1904 (Box 7, Folder 230)
    - Nelson, Knute, 15 items, 1905-21 (Box 7, Folder 231)
    - Noble, John W., 4 items, 1889-1911 (Box 7, Folder 232)
    - Norcross, George, 11 items, 1880-1908, n.d.
    - Northrop, Birdsley G., 3 items, 1883 (Box 7, Folder 233)
    - "O" general, 9 items, 1878-1922 (Box 7, Folder 234)
    - Ogden, Robert C., 1 item, 1880 (Box 7, Folder 235)
    - Ohettoint, 1 item, 1878
    - Olmsted, Marlin E., 8 items, 1903-08 (Box 7, Folder 236)
    - Oskison, John M., 3 items, 1908, 1913
    - Ostrander, L. A., 6 items, 1920, 1922-23 (Box 7, Folder 237)
    - Owen, Robert L., 4 items, 1909-17
    - "Pa-Pe" general, 18 items, 1878-1924, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 238)
    - "Pi" general, 13 items, 1877-1922, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 239)
    - "Po-Pu" general, 14 items, 1879-1923, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 240)
    - Parker, Arthur C., 11 items, 1912-13 (Box 7, Folder 241)
    - Parker, Arthur C., 14 items, 1914-15 (Box 7, Folder 242)
    - Parker, Arthur C., 20 items, 1916-23 (Box 7, Folder 243)
    - Parker, Gabe E., 1 item, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 244)
    - The Patriotic League
      See: Wilson L. Gill, Box 3, folder 108
    - Paul, Louis F., 6 items, 1920-21, 1923
    - Paul, William L., 6 items, 1921-23 (Box 7, Folder 245)
    - Pedrick, Laura D., 4 items, 1893-1920 (Box 7, Folder 246)
    - Peel, Samuel W., 3 items, 1888, 1892
    - Pendleton, Alice K., 6 items, 1876-78 (Box 7, Folder 247)
    - Penoi, Mark, 2 items, 1919-20
    - Perkins, Bishop W., 3 items, 1888-92 (Box 7, Folder 248)
    - Peter, Fannie L., 7 items, 1904-23, n.d.
    - Pierce, Mr. and Mrs. Bemus (Box 7, Folder 249)
    - Platt, Mrs. E. G., 5 items, 1886-1902
    - Pollock, William J., 2 items, 1882 (Box 7, Folder 250)
    - Pound, Thaddeus C., 6 items, 1880-81
    - Powell, John W., 1 item, 1877 (Box 7, Folder 251)
    - Pratt, Daniel D., 2 items, 1873-74
    - Price, Hiram, 2 items, 1883 (Box 7, Folder 252)
    - Prince, Morris W., 2 items, 1905, 1920
    - Proctor, Edna Dean, 19 items, 1891-1907, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 253)
    - Proctor, Redfield, 6 items, 1889-98 (Box 7, Folder 254)
    - Public Ledger
      See: John J. Spurgeon, Box 8, folder 289
    - "Q" general, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 255)
    - Quarles, Joseph V., 3 items, 1901, 1903 (Box 7, Folder 256)
    - Quay, Matthew S., 1898-99
    - "Ra-Re" general, 9 items, 1867-1904, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 257)
    - "Ri-Ru" general, 13 items, 1875-1920, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 258)
    - Red Fox Skiuhushu, 1 item, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 259)
    - Reid, Whitelaw, 1 item, 1876
    - Rhoads, James E., 6 items, 1881-94 (Box 7, Folder 260)
    - Richards, Charles L., 1 item, 1923 (Box 7, Folder 261)
    - Riddick, Carl W., 6 items, 1919-22
    - Riggs, Stephen R., 2 items, 1881-82 (Box 8, Folder 262)
    - Riordan, D. M., 9 items, 1883
    - Robbins, J. C., 2 items, 1879 (Box 8, Folder 263)
    - Robe, Chauncey Y.
      See: Chauncey Yellow Robe, Box 9, folder 337
    - Robertson, Alice M., 4 items, 1882-1902, [1920?] (Box 8, Folder 264)
    - Robertson, Ann Eliza W., 3 items, 1898-1903
    - Robinson, Joseph T., 2 items, 1915 (Box 8, Folder 265)
    - Rogers, Edward L., 3 items, 1920-21
    - Roosevelt, Theodore, 3 items, 1901 (Box 8, Folder 266)
    - Ross, Lucretia T., 2 items, 1908
    - Rust, Horatio N., 1 item, 1891 (Box 8, Folder 267)
    - "Sa-Se" general, 18 items, 1879-1920, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 268)
    - "Sh-Sk" general, 18 items, 1877-1920, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 269)
    - "Sm-Sp" general, 18 items, 1896-1923, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 270)
    - "St-Sw" general, 15 items, 1893-1923, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 271)
    - Safford, W. E., 5 items, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 272)
    - Sage, Margaret O. S. (Mrs. Russell Sage), 13 items, 1882-1913, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 273)
    - Sauvé, Alex C., 1 item, 1916 (Box 8, Folder 274)
    - Schurz, Carl, 12 items, 1879-1904, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 275)
    - Seelye, Laurenus C., 1 item, 1898 (Box 8, Folder 276)
    - Sells, Cato, 13 items, 1913-18 (Box 8, Folder 277)
    - Semple, C. M., 5 items, 1879-90 (Box 8, Folder 278)
    - Shafter, William R., 1 item, 1901 (Box 8, Folder 279)
    - Sherman, James S., 26 items, 1896-1909 (Box 8, Folder 280)
    - Sherman, William T., 3 items, 1876-77, 1880 (Box 8, Folder 281)
    - Sickles, Daniel E., 2 items, 1903
    - Sinclair, Upton, 3 items, 1923 (Box 8, Folder 282)
    - Six killer, Sam, 3 items, 1899-1920
    - Sloan, Thomas L., 11 items, 1909-24 (Box 8, Folder 283)
    - Smiley, Albert K., 5 items, 1883-92 (Box 8, Folder 284)
    - Smiley, Daniel, 2 items, 1914
    - Smoot, Reed, 1 item, 1916 (Box 8, Folder 285)
    - Sniffen, Matthew K., 9 items, 1913-19
    - Snowden, A. Louden, 5 items, 1887 (Box 8, Folder 286)
    - Sparhawk, Frances G., 5 items, 1919-23 (Box 8, Folder 287)
    - Spencer, (Mrs.) Dorcas J., 5 items, 1922
    - Spencer, Selden P., 2 items, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 288)
    - Spinner, Francis E., 1 item, 1877
    - Spurgeon, John J., 1 item, 1916 (Box 8, Folder 289)
    - Spybuck, Thomas, 1 item, 1920
    - Standing, Alfred J., 6 items, 1878-1901 (Box 8, Folder 290)
    - Standing Bear, Luther, 2 items, 1911, 1920
    - Stars, Clarence T., 1 item, 1903 (Box 8, Folder 291)
    - Stephens, John H., 2 items, 1916
    - Sterling, Matthew and Mrs., 5 items, 1919-23 (Box 8, Folder 292)
    - Stevens, E. L., 20 items, 1882-89 (Box 8, Folder 293)
    - Stouch, Geo. W. H.
    - Strong, Josiah, 1 item, 1895 (Box 8, Folder 294)
    - Stryker, M. Woolsey, 4 items, 1899-1900, 1910
    - Sunset Magazine
      See: Walter V. Woehlke, box 9, folder 331
    - Sutherland, Dan, 1 item, 1923 (Box 8, Folder 295)
    - "T" general, 22 items, 1876-1922, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 296)
    - Tadu, Shisoshi, 6 items, 1894-96 (Box 8, Folder 297)
    - Taft, William Howard, 3 items, 1905-10
    - Tatum, Lawrie, 1896 (Box 8, Folder 298)
    - Teller, Mr. and Mrs. Henry Moore, 14 items, 1882-1904
    - Thaw, Mr. and Mrs. William, 11 items, 1883-97, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 299)
    - Thomas, Elmer, 2 items, 1923
    - Thompson, Royal W., 4 items, 1903 (Box 8, Folder 300)
    - Tibbett, Jonathan, 5 items, 1920-21 (Box 8, Folder 301)
    - Tourgée, Albion W., 1 item, 1892
    - Townsend, E. B., 1 item, 1883 (Box 8, Folder 302)
    - Trumbull, Henry Clay, 1 item, 1882
    - Tsait-kope-ta, Paul C., 2 items, 1880-81 (Box 8, Folder 303)
    - Tsukamoto, Fuji, 6 items, 1892-1904
    - "U" general, 5 items, 1880-1923 (Box 8, Folder 304)
    - United States Dept. of Interior, Office of Indian Affairs, Commissioner
    - United States Dept. of Interior, Secretary
    - "V" general, 8 items, 1899-1923, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 305)
    - Van Voorhis, John, 1 item, 1881 (Box 9, Folder 306)
    - Vaux, George, Jr., 13 items, 1887-1913
    - Venne, Alfred M., 2 items, 1904, 1907 (Box 9, Folder 307)
    - Vetter, Josie, 13 items, 1904-23
    - Vilas, William Freeman, 5 items, 1888-93, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 308)
    - "Wa-We" general, 10 items, 1901-1920, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 309)
    - "Wh" general, 11 items, 1879-1920, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 310)
    - "Wi" general, 14 items, 1879-1923, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 311)
    - "Wo-Wr" general, 16 items, 1879-1922, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 312)
    - Waldo, Fullerton L., 1 item, 1911 (Box 9, Folder 313)
    - Wanamaker, John, 3 items, 1879, 1913
    - Ward, William Hayes, 5 items, 1888-1903 (Box 9, Folder 314)
    - Warner, Glenn S., 1 item, 1904 (Box 9, Folder 315)
    - Wasson, C. W., 1 item, 1892 (Box 9, Folder 316)
    - Wasson, James B., 4 items, 1890-1900
    - Wausakakamick, Sarah A. Williams, 4 items, 1920-21 (Box 9, Folder 317)
    - Weaver, John
    - Wellborn, Olin, 1 item, 1886 (Box 9, Folder 318)
    - Wells, J. D., 2 items, 1877
    - Welsh, Herbert, 10 items, 1884-92 (Box 9, Folder 319)
    - Welsh, Herbert, 7 items, 1914, 1917-18 (Box 9, Folder 320)
    - Wetherell, George S., 7 items, 1910-20, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 321)
    - Wheeler, Joseph, 1 item, 1900 (Box 9, Folder 322)
    - Wheelock, Dennison, 18 items, 1900-23 (Box 9, Folder 323)
    - Whipple, Henry Benjamin, 15 items, 1876-78 (Box 9, Folder 324)
    - Whipple, Henry Benjamin, 1879-1901, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 325)
    - White Buffalo, 14 items, 1902 (Box 9, Folder 326)
    - Whittlesey, E., 17 items, 1884-97 (Box 9, Folder 327)
    - Wicks, J. B., 6 items, 1879, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 328)
    - Wilkinson, Melville C., 10 items, 1879-98, n.d.
    - Willard, Francis E., 1 item, 1892 (Box 9, Folder 329)
    - Williams, Edward H., 4 items, 1891, 1898
    - Wilson, James H., 4 items, 1908-1919 (Box 9, Folder 330)
    - Wistar, E. M., 6 items, 1910-17
    - Woehlke, Walter V., 6 items, 1921-23 (Box 9, Folder 331)
    - Woman's Heart, 1 item, 1877
    - Wood, Leonard, 4 items, 1917-21 (Box 9, Folder 332)
    - Wood, Mariette, 1 item, 1904
    - Wotherspoon, W. W., 19 items, 1891-94 (Box 9, Folder 333)
    - Wotherspoon, W. W., 13 items, 1897-1915 (Box 9, Folder 334)
    - Wright, Henry, 2 items, 1881-82 (Box 9, Folder 335)
    - Wright, James G., 5 items, 1883-85, n.d.
    - "Y" general, 2 items, 1920, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 336)
    - Yellow Robe, Chauncey, 13 items, 1897-1917 (Box 9, Folder 337)
    - Yellow Robe, Chauncey, 14 items, 1918-23 (Box 9, Folder 338)
    - "Z" general, 3 items, 1878, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 339)
    - Unidentified, 13 items, 1879-1923, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 340)
  - OUTGOING LETTERS
    Boxes 10-1 through 10-60 contain bound volumes of letterpress copies.
    - 1872 Nov-1874 Jun (Box 10-1)
    - 1876 Aug-1877 Nov (Box 10-2)
    - 1877 Nov-1878 Apr (Box 10-3)
    - 1879 Dec-1881 Jun (Box 10-4)
    - 1881 Jun-1882 Aug (Box 10-5)
    - 1882 Sep-1883 Jun (Box 10-6)
    - 1883 Jun-1883 Dec (Box 10-7)
    - 1883 Dec-1884 Jun (Box 10-8)
    - 1884 Jun-1885 Jan (Box 10-9)
    - 1885 Jan-1885 Oct (Box 10-10)
    - 1885 Oct-1886 May (Box 10-11)
    - 1886 May-1887 May (Box 10-12)
    - 1887 May-1888 Feb (Box 10-13)
    - 1888 Feb-1889 Mar (Box 10-14)
    - 1889 Mar-1889 Nov (Box 10-15)
    - 1889 Nov-1890 Jun (Box 10-16)
    - 1890 Jun-1891 Jan (Box 10-17)
    - 1891 Jan-1891 May (Box 10-18)
    - 1891 May-1891 Oct (Box 10-19)
    - 1891 Oct-1892 Feb (Box 10-20)
    - 1892 Feb-1892 Jun (Box 10-21)
    - 1892 Jun-1892 Dec (Box 10-22)
    - 1892 Dec-1893 Jul (Box 10-23)
    - 1893 Jul-1894 Feb (Box 10-24)
    - 1894 Feb-1894 May (Box 10-25)
    - 1894 May-1894 Nov (Box 10-26)
    - 1894 Nov-1895 Mar (Box 10-27)
    - 1895 Mar-1895 Aug (Box 10-28)
    - 1895 Aug-1896 Jan (Box 10-29)
    - 1896 Jan-1896 Jun (Box 10-30)
    - 1896 Jun-1897 Feb (Box 10-31)
    - 1897 Feb-1897 Jun (Box 10-32)
    - 1897 Jun-1898 Jan (Box 10-33)
    - 1898 Jan-1898 Jun (Box 10-34)
    - 1898 Jun-1899 Jan (Box 10-35)
    - 1899 Jan-1899 May (Box 10-36)
    - 1899 May-1899 Jul (Box 10-37)
    - 1899 Jul-1899 Oct (Box 10-38)
    - 1899 Oct-1900 Jan (Box 10-39)
    - 1900 Jan-1900 Mar (Box 10-40)
    - 1900 Mar-1900 Apr (Box 10-41)
    - 1900 Apr-1900 Jul (Box 10-42)
    - 1900 Jul-1900 Oct (Box 10-43)
    - 1900 Oct-1901 Jan (Box 10-44)
    - 1901 Jan-1901 Apr (Box 10-45)
    - 1901 Apr-1901 Jun (Box 10-46)
    - 1901 Jun-1901 Aug (Box 10-47)
    - 1901 Aug-1901 Nov (Box 10-48)
    - 1901 Nov-1902 Feb (Box 10-49)
    - 1902 Feb-1902 Jun (Box 10-50)
    - 1902 Jun-1902 Aug (Box 10-51)
    - 1902 Aug-1902 Nov (Box 10-52)
    - 1902 Nov-1903 Jan (Box 10-53)
    - 1903 Jan-1903 Apr (Box 10-54)
    - 1903 Apr-1903 Jul (Box 10-55)
    - 1903 Jul-1903 Oct (Box 10-56)
    - 1903 Oct-1904 Feb (Box 10-57)
    - 1904 Feb-1904 May (Box 10-58)
    - 1904 May-1904 Jun (Box 10-59)
    - Sioux Commission: 1888 Jun-1889 May (Box 10-60)
    - Unbound letters, 4 items, 1878-79 (Box 10-61, Folder 341)
    - Unbound letters, 6 items, 1881-83, 1887 (Box 10-61, Folder 342)
    - Unbound letters, 8 items, 1892-1902 (Box 10-61, Folder 343)
    - Unbound letters, 10 items, 1903 Jan (Box 10-61, Folder 344)
    - Unbound letters, 8 items, 1903 Feb (Box 10-61, Folder 345)
    - Unbound letters, 2 items, 1903 Sep-Nov (Box 10-61, Folder 346)
    - Unbound letters, 8 items, 1904 (Box 10-61, Folder 347)
    - Unbound letters, 2 items, 1905 (Box 10-61, Folder 348)
    - Unbound letters, 11 items, 1906 (Box 10-61, Folder 349)
    - Unbound letters, 15 items, 1907 (Box 10-61, Folder 350)
    - Unbound letters, 12 items, 1908 Jan (Box 10-61, Folder 351)
    - Unbound letters, 16 items, 1908 Feb-Dec (Box 10-61, Folder 352)
    - Unbound letters, 15 items, 1909 (Box 10-61, Folder 353)
    - Unbound letters, 18 items, 1910 (Box 10-61, Folder 354)
    - Unbound letters, 14 items, 1911 (Box 10-61, Folder 355)
    - Unbound letters, 14 items, 1912 (Box 10-61, Folder 356)
    - Unbound letters, 18 items, 1913 Jan-May (Box 10-61, Folder 357)
    - Unbound letters, 20 items, 1913 Jun-Oct (Box 10-61, Folder 358)
    - Unbound letters, 14 items, 1913 Nov-Dec (Box 10-61, Folder 359)
    - Unbound letters, 28 items, 1914 Jan-Apr (Box 10-61, Folder 360)
    - Unbound letters, 23 items, 1914 May-Jun (Box 10-61, Folder 361)
    - Unbound letters, 21 items, 1914 Jul-Aug (Box 10-61, Folder 362)
    - Unbound letters, 15 items, 1914 Sep-Dec (Box 10-61, Folder 363)
    - Unbound letters, 16 items, 1915 Jan-Apr (Box 11, Folder 364)
    - Unbound letters, 30 items, 1915 May-Nov (Box 11, Folder 365)
    - Unbound letters, 11 items, 1915 Dec (Box 11, Folder 366)
    - Unbound letters, 11 items, 1916 Jan (Box 11, Folder 367)
    - Unbound letters, 9 items, 1916 Feb (Box 11, Folder 368)
    - Unbound letters, 11 items, 1916 Mar-Apr (Box 11, Folder 369)
    - Unbound letters, 9 items, 1916 May-Jun (Box 11, Folder 370)
    - Unbound letters, 19 items, 1916 Jul-Aug (Box 11, Folder 371)
    - Unbound letters, 9 items, 1916 Sep-Oct (Box 11, Folder 372)
    - Unbound letters, 10 items, 1916 Nov-Dec (Box 11, Folder 373)
    - Unbound letters, 11 items, 1917 Jan-Feb (Box 11, Folder 374)
    - Unbound letters, 21 items, 1917 Mar (Box 11, Folder 375)
    - Unbound letters, 10 items, 1917 Apr (Box 11, Folder 376)
    - Unbound letters, 13 items, 1917 May (Box 11, Folder 377)
    - Unbound letters, 7 items, 1917 Jun-Jul (Box 11, Folder 378)
    - Unbound letters, 10 items, 1917 Aug (Box 11, Folder 379)
    - Unbound letters, 8 items, 1917 Sep-Oct (Box 11, Folder 380)
    - Unbound letters, 24 items, 1917 Nov-Dec (Box 11, Folder 381)
    - Unbound letters, 11 items, 1918 Jan (Box 11, Folder 382)
    - Unbound letters, 13 items, 1918 Feb (Box 11, Folder 383)
    - Unbound letters, 8 items, 1918 Mar (Box 11, Folder 384)
    - Unbound letters, 10 items, 1918 Apr (Box 11, Folder 385)
    - Unbound letters, 14 items, 1918 May-Jun (Box 11, Folder 386)
    - Unbound letters, 8 items, 1918 Jul-Aug (Box 11, Folder 387)
    - Unbound letters, 10 items, 1918 Sep-Nov (Box 11, Folder 388)
    - Unbound letters, 11 items, 1918 Dec (Box 11, Folder 389)
    - Unbound letters, 13 items, 1919 Jan (Box 11, Folder 390)
    - Unbound letters, 11 items, 1919 Feb (Box 11, Folder 391)
    - Unbound letters, 22 items, 1919 Mar-Apr (Box 11, Folder 392)
    - Unbound letters, 12 items, 1919 May (Box 11, Folder 393)
    - Unbound letters, 14 items, 1919 Jun (Box 11, Folder 394)
    - Unbound letters, 16 items, 1919 Jul-Aug (Box 11, Folder 395)
    - Unbound letters, 17 items, 1919 Sep-Oct (Box 11, Folder 396)
    - Unbound letters, 15 items, 1919 Nov-Dec (Box 11, Folder 397)
    - Unbound letters, 12 items, 1920 Jan (Box 11, Folder 398)
    - Unbound letters, 17 items, 1920 Feb (Box 11, Folder 399)
    - Unbound letters, 9 items, 1920 Mar (Box 12, Folder 400)
    - Unbound letters, 31 items, 1920 Apr (Box 12, Folder 401)
    - Unbound letters, 14 items, 1920 May (Box 12, Folder 402)
    - Unbound letters, 11 items, 1920 Jun-Jul (Box 12, Folder 403)
    - Unbound letters, 13 items, 1920 Sep-Oct (Box 12, Folder 404)
    - Unbound letters, 13 items, 1920 Nov-Dec (Box 12, Folder 405)
    - Unbound letters, 25 items, 1921 Jan 8-18 (Box 12, Folder 406)
    - Unbound letters, 23 items, 1921 Jan 19-31 (Box 12, Folder 407)
    - Unbound letters, 20 items, 1921 Feb (Box 12, Folder 408)
    - Unbound letters, 15 items, 1921 Mar (Box 12, Folder 409)
    - Unbound letters, 15 items, 1921 Apr (Box 12, Folder 410)
    - Unbound letters, 15 items, 1921 May-Jun (Box 12, Folder 411)